<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jason Moy</title>
    <link>https://jasonmoy.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jason Moy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href = &#34;mailto:jmoy1@uw.edu&#34; target = &#34;_blank&#34; rel = &#34;noopener&#34;&gt; jmoy1@uw.edu &lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jasonmoy.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An introduction to psycModel</title>
      <link>https://jasonmoy.us/post/psycmodel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonmoy.us/post/psycmodel/</guid>
      <description>At its core, this package allows people to analyze their data with one simple function call. For example, when you are running a linear regression, you need to fit the model, check the goodness of fit (e.g., R2), check the model assumption, and plot the interaction (if the interaction is included). Without this package, you need several packages to do the above steps. Additionally, if you are an R beginner, you probably don’t know where to find all these R packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jasonmoy.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonmoy.us/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am a second-year PhD student in Organizational Behavior at the Foster School of Business, University of Washington. My research interest primarily centers on how societal and cultural norms shape individuals&amp;rsquo; behaviors and the work experiences of underprivileged individuals. Beyond my research, I have also developed an R package (pscyModel) aimed at simplifying statistical analysis in R. It is currently distributed through CRAN, and the development version can be accessed on my GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jasonmoy.us/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonmoy.us/contact/</guid>
      <description>Jason Moy
Department of Management and Organization
Michael G. Foster School of Business
University of Washington
Seattle, WA 98195
Email: jmoy1@uw.edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://jasonmoy.us/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonmoy.us/cv/</guid>
      <description>Please click the link to view my CV</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://jasonmoy.us/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonmoy.us/research/</guid>
      <description>Manuscripts in Revision/Under Review  Moy, J. H., Van Dyne, A., &amp;amp; Hattrup, K (in press). The Contingent Consequences of Job Insecurity: A Cross- National Investigation of the Effects of Job Insecurity, Employability, and Culture on Employee Outcomes. Journal of Cross-Cultural Psychology.  Selected Works-in-Progress  Moy, J. H. [data collection]. Is Telecommuting Beneficial to All Cultures? A Multinational Investigation.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
